Language:  

    * Editions
        
    * Technology
        
    * Frequently asked questions
        
    * Product comparison

    * [Order trial system](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/trial/)    /    [Initial consultation](https://calendly.com/bluespicewiki/initial-consultation-w)    /    [Find partner](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/order/find-partner/)   /   [Prices](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/prices/configure-your-price/)

    * Use Cases
        
    * Success Stories
        
    * Development & integrations

    * [Order trial system](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/trial/)    /    [Initial consultation](https://calendly.com/bluespicewiki/initial-consultation-w)    /    [Find partner](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/order/find-partner/)   /   [Prices](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/prices/configure-your-price/)

    * Services
        
    * Trainings & workshops
        
    * Learning

    * [Order trial system](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/trial/)    /    [Initial consultation](https://calendly.com/bluespicewiki/initial-consultation-w)    /    [Find partner](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/order/find-partner/)   /   [Prices](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/prices/configure-your-price/)

    * Prices
        
    * Order
        
    * Frequently asked questions

    * [Order trial system](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/trial/)    /    [Initial consultation](https://calendly.com/bluespicewiki/initial-consultation-w)    /    [Find partner](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/order/find-partner/)   /   [Prices](http://bluespice.com.dedi7975.your-server.de/buy/prices/configure-your-price/)

Privacy2024-09-02T10:24:12+02:00

Privacy policy
==============

We take data protection seriously.
----------------------------------

The protection of your privacy when processing personal data is an important concern for us. When you visit our website, our web servers store the IP of your Internet service provider, the website from which you visit us, the web pages you visit on our site and the date and duration of your visit as standard. This information is absolutely necessary for the technical transmission of the web pages and secure server operation. A personalized evaluation of this data does not take place.

If you send us data via contact form, this data will be stored on our servers in the course of data backup. Your data will only be used by us to process your request. Your data will be treated strictly confidential. It will not be passed on to third parties.

Responsible:

Hallo Welt! GmbH  
Bruderwöhrdstraße 29  
93055 Regensburg, Germany

Phone: +49 941 – 660 800  
E-mail: [info@hallowelt.com](mailto:info@hallowelt.com)

Personal data
-------------

Personal data are data about your person. This includes your name, address and email address. You do not have to disclose any personal data to visit our website. In some cases we need your name and address as well as other information to be able to offer you the requested service.

The same applies in the case that we supply you with information material on request or when we answer your inquiries. In these cases we will always point this out to you. In addition, we only store the data that you have transmitted to us automatically or voluntarily.

When you use one of our services, we usually only collect the data that is necessary to provide you with our service. We may ask you for additional information, but this is voluntary. Whenever we process personal data, we do so to provide you with our service or to pursue our commercial objectives.

Contacting
----------

When contacting us (e.g. via contact form, email, telephone or via social media), the information of the inquiring persons is processed, if necessary in order to respond to the requests and to any requested actions.

The response to the contact inquiries in the context of contractual or pre-contractual relationships is carried out to fulfill our contractual obligations or to respond to (pre)contractual inquiries and otherwise on the basis of legitimate interests in responding to the inquiries.

* Types of data processed: inventory data (e.g. names, addresses), contact data (e.g. e-mail, telephone numbers), content data (e.g. entries in online forms).
* Data subjects: Communication partners.
* Purposes of processing: contact requests and communication.
* Legal basis: Contract performance and pre-contractual inquiries (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b. GDPR), Legitimate interests (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f. GDPR).

Automatically stored data
-------------------------

### Server log files

The provider of the pages automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser automatically transmits to us. These are:

* Date and time of the request
* Name of the requested file
* Page from which the file was requested
* access status (file transferred, file not found, etc.)
* Web browser and operating system used
* complete IP address of the requesting computer
* amount of data transferred

This data is not merged with other data sources. The processing is carried out in accordance with Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR on the basis of our legitimate interest in improving the stability and functionality of our website.

For reasons of technical security, in particular to defend against attempted attacks on our web server, we store this data for a short period of time. It is not possible for us to draw conclusions about individual persons on the basis of this data. After seven days at the latest, the data is anonymized by shortening the IP address at domain level, so that it is no longer possible to establish a link to the individual user. The data is also processed anonymously for statistical purposes; it is not compared with other data or passed on to third parties, even in part. Only within the context of our server statistics, which we publish every two years in our activity report, is a presentation of the number of page views made.

Cookies
-------

When you visit our website, we may store information on your computer in the form of cookies. Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID. A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie. It consists of a string of characters by which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored. This enables the visited Internet pages and servers to distinguish the individual browser of the data subject from other Internet browsers that contain other cookies. A specific Internet browser can be recognized and identified via the unique cookie ID.

Through the use of session cookies, the responsible party can provide the users of this website with a user-friendly service that would not be possible without the cookie setting. Without consent, we only use technically necessary cookies on the legal basis of legitimate interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR.

We only use personal cookies to improve our website or for marketing/advertising purposes with your consent. On your first visit, you can voluntarily agree to tracking or analysis via the cookie banner that appears. If necessary, your data will be passed on to partners or third-party providers. Only if you explicitly agree to this will these cookies be stored, the legal basis is then your consent in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR.

You can change your settings for the use of cookies at any time.

Borlabs Cookie
--------------

Our website uses the cookie consent technology of Borlabs Cookie to obtain your consent to store certain cookies in your browser and to document this consent in accordance with data protection law. The provider of this technology is Borlabs – Benjamin A. Bornschein, Rübenkamp 32, 22305 Hamburg (hereinafter Borlabs).

When you enter our website, a Borlabs cookie is stored in your browser, in which the consents you have given or the revocation of these consents are stored. This data is not shared with the Borlabs cookie provider.

The collected data will be stored until you request us to delete it or until you delete the Borlabs cookie yourself or until the purpose for storing the data no longer applies. Mandatory legal retention periods remain unaffected. Details on the data processing of Borlabs Cookie can be found at https://de.borlabs.io/kb/welche-daten-speichert-borlabs-cookie/.

Borlabs Cookie Consent Technology is used to obtain the legally required consent for the use of cookies. The legal basis for this is Art. 6 para. 1 p. 1 lit. c GDPR.

We have concluded a contract on order processing (AV) pursuant to Art. 28 DSGVO with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that the provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

Cloudflare
----------

We use the service “Cloudflare”. The provider is Cloudflare Inc, 101 Townsend St., San Francisco, CA 94107, USA (hereinafter referred to as “Cloudflare”).

Cloudflare offers a globally distributed content delivery network with DNS. This technically information transfer between your browser and our website is routed via the Cloudflare network. Cloudflare network. This enables Cloudflare to analyze the data traffic between your browser between your browser and our website and to act as a filter between our servers and potentially malicious traffic from the internet. Internet. Cloudflare may also use cookies or other technologies to technologies to recognize Internet users, but these are used solely for the purpose used solely for the purpose described here.

The use of Cloudflare is based on our legitimate interest in the most error-free and error-free and secure provision of our website (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR).

The data transfer to the USA is based on the standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found here: [https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

Further information on security and data protection at Cloudflare can be found here: [https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

We have concluded an order processing contract (AV) in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that the provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

Creative Commons
----------------

This website uses the analytics service Creative Commons. The provider is Paul Klimpel, Till Kreutzer, c/o iRights e.V, Almstadtstr. 9/11,10119 Berlin, Germany.

Creative Commons allows us to analyze the behavior of our website visitors. For this purpose, Name collects, among other things, your shortened e-mail address, geo-information, IP address, log files and other information that your browser transmits to our web server when you visit the website.

This allows us to measure website interactions, such as length of stay, conversions (e.g. registrations, orders), scroll events, clicks and page views of the website visitor. These interactions are assigned to the website visitor for the duration of the current day so that they can be recognized on subsequent visits. After the end of the day, visitor recognition is no longer possible.

Without your consent, no cookies are stored in your browser and no information is read from the memory of your end device. The cookie-free use of this analysis tool is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR.

The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior in order to optimize both its website and its advertising. The rights and fundamental freedoms of the data subjects are safeguarded. The IP address is anonymized as early as possible during the analysis with Creative Commons and visitor recognition is only possible for the duration of the current day.

If a corresponding consent has been requested, the processing is carried out exclusively on the basis of on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 para. 1 TTDSG. Consent can be revoked at any time.

We have concluded an order processing contract (AV) in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that the provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

Further details can be found in the Creative Commons privacy policy at: [https://de.creativecommons.net/privacy/](https://de.creativecommons.net/privacy/)

Discourse
---------

We use the service ” Discourse”. The provider is Civilized Discourse Construction Kit, Inc., 78 Allée Primavera, Centre UBIDOCA, 15232, Pringy, 74370 ANNECY, FRANCE.

Discourse offers a globally distributed content delivery network with DNS. This technical information transfer between your browser and our website is routed via the Discourse network. This enables Discourse to analyze the data traffic between your browser between your browser and our website and to act as a filter between our servers and potentially malicious traffic from the internet. Internet. Discourse may also use cookies or other technologies to technologies to recognize Internet users, but these are used solely for the purpose used solely for the purpose described here.

The use of Discourse is based on our legitimate interest in the most error-free and error-free and secure provision of our website (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR).

The data transfer to the USA is based on the standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found here: [https://www.discourse.org/privacy](https://www.discourse.org/privacy)

Further information on security and data protection at Cloudflare can be found here: [https://www.discourse.org/privacy](https://www.discourse.org/privacy)

We have concluded an order processing contract (AV) in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that the provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

Google Ads
----------

The website operator uses Google Ads. Google Ads is an online advertising program of Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

Google Ads enables us to display advertisements in the Google search engine or on third party websites when the user enters certain search terms on Google (keyword targeting). Furthermore, targeted advertisements can be played on the basis of the user data available at Google (e. g. location data and interests) can be displayed (target group targeting). We as website operator can evaluate this data quantitatively by analyzing, for example, which search terms led to the display of our ads and how many ads led to corresponding clicks.

The use of this service is based on your consent in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 Para. 1 TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time. Data transfer to the USA is based on the standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found here: [https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks) and [https://privacy.google.com/businesses/controllerterms/mccs/](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/controllerterms/mccs/).

Google Analytics
----------------

This website uses functions of the web analysis service Google Analytics. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

Google Analytics enables the website operator to analyze the behavior of website visitors. In doing so, the website operator receives various usage data, such as page views, length of stay, operating systems used and the origin of the user. This data is assigned to the respective end device of the user. An assignment to a device ID does not take place.

Furthermore, we can use Google Analytics to record, among other things, your mouse and scroll movements and clicks. Furthermore, Google Analytics uses various modeling approaches to supplement the collected data sets and uses machine learning technologies in the data analysis.

Google Analytics uses technologies that enable the recognition of the user for the purpose of analyzing user behavior (e.g. cookies or device fingerprinting). The information collected by Google about the use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there.

The use of this service is based on your consent according to Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 para. 1 TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time. Data transfer to the USA is based on the standard contractual clauses of the EU Commission. Details can be found here: https://privacy.google.com/businesses/controllerterms/mccs/.

We use Google signals. When you visit our website, Google Analytics records, among other things, your location, search history and YouTube history, as well as demographic data (visitor data). This data can be used for personalized advertising with the help of Google signals. If you have a Google account, Google Signal’s visitor data is linked to your Google account and used for personalized advertising messages. The data is also used to create anonymized statistics on the user behavior of our users.

We have concluded a contract on order processing (AV) pursuant to Art. 28 GDPR with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that this provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

This website uses the “e-commerce measurement” function of Google Analytics. With the help of e-commerce measurement, the website operator can analyze the purchasing behavior of website visitors to improve its online marketing campaigns. This involves recording information such as orders placed, average order values, shipping costs and the time from viewing to purchasing a product. This data can be summarized by Google under a transaction ID, which is assigned to the respective user or his device.

Google Tag Manager
------------------

We use the Google Tag Manager. The provider is Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

The Google Tag Manager is a tool that enables us to integrate tracking or statistical tools and other technologies on our website. The Google Tag Manager itself does not create user profiles, does not store cookies and does not perform any independent analyses. It only serves to manage and play out the tools integrated via it. However, the Google Tag Manager records your IP address, which may also be transmitted to Google’s parent company in the United States.

The use of the Google Tag Manager is based on Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in a quick and uncomplicated integration and management of various tools on its website. If a corresponding consent has been requested, the processing is carried out exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 para. 1 TTDSG, insofar as the consent includes the storage of cookies or access to information in the user’s terminal device (e.g. device fingerprinting) as defined by the TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time.

Google Web Fonts (local hosting)
--------------------------------

This site uses so-called web fonts provided by Google for the uniform display of fonts. The Google Fonts are installed locally. A connection to Google servers does not take place.

Further information on Google Web Fonts can be found at [https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq) and in Google’s privacy policy: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de).

ajax.googleapis.com/ jQuery
---------------------------

We use Ajax and jQuery technologies on this site to optimize loading speeds. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland. In this regard, program libraries are called from Google servers. The CDN (content delivery network) of Google is used. If you have previously used jQuery on another page of the Google CDN, your browser will fall back on the copy stored in the cache. If this is not the case, this will require a download, whereby data from your browser will be sent to Google! Your data will be transferred to the USA. You can find out more on the provider’s website. [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de&gl=de](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de&gl=de)

WordPress
---------

This website uses WordPress. WordPress is a free content management system by Automattic Inc. for blogs and websites. Location of the provider: USA.

WordPress allows us to analyze the behavior of our website visitors. For this purpose, WordPress collects, among other things, IP addresses that your browser transmits to our web server when you visit the website. These interactions are assigned to the website visitor for the duration of the current day, so that he or she can be recognized on subsequent visits. After the end of the day, visitor recognition is no longer possible.

Without your consent, no cookies are stored in your browser and no information is read from the memory of your terminal device. The cookie-free use of this analysis tool is based on Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior in order to optimize both its web offering and its advertising. The rights and fundamental freedoms of the data subjects are preserved. The IP address is anonymized as early as possible during the analysis with WordPress and visitor recognition is possible for the duration of the current day at the most.

If a corresponding consent has been requested, the processing is carried out exclusively on the basis of basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 para. 1 TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time.

We have concluded a contract on order processing (AV) pursuant to Art. 28 GDPR with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that this provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

For further details, please refer to the WordPress privacy policy at: [https://de.wordpress.org/about/privacy/](https://de.wordpress.org/about/privacy/)

YouTube
-------

This website embeds videos from YouTube. The operator of the pages is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

We use YouTube in extended data protection mode. According to YouTube, this mode has the effect that YouTube does not store any information about visitors to this website before they watch the video. However, the transfer of data to YouTube partners is not necessarily excluded by the extended data protection mode. Thus, YouTube – regardless of whether you watch a video – establishes a connection to the Google DoubleClick network.

As soon as you start a YouTube video on this website, a connection to the servers of YouTube servers is established. This tells the YouTube server which of our pages you have visited. If you are logged into your YouTube account, you enable YouTube to assign your surfing behavior directly to your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account.

Furthermore, YouTube can save various cookies on your end device after starting a video or use comparable recognition technologies (e.g. device fingerprinting). In this way, YouTube can obtain information about visitors to this website. This information is used, among other things, to collect video statistics, improve the user experience, and prevent fraud attempts.

If necessary, further data processing operations may be triggered after the start of a YouTube video, over which we have no control.

may be triggered after the start of a YouTube video, over which we have no control. YouTube is used in the interest of an appealing presentation of our online offers. This represents a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR Insofar as a corresponding consent has been requested, the processing is carried out exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 para. 1 TTDSG, insofar as the consent includes the storage of cookies or access to information in the user’s terminal device (e.g. device fingerprinting) within the meaning of the TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time.

For more information about data protection at YouTube, please see their privacy policy at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de).

Google Doubleclick
------------------

This website uses functions of Google DoubleClick. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, (hereinafter “DoubleClick”).

DoubleClick is used to display interest-based advertisements to you throughout the Google advertising network.

advertising network. The advertisements can be targeted to the interests of the respective viewer with the help of DoubleClick. For example, our ads may be displayed in Google search results or in banner ads associated with DoubleClick.

In order to be able to display interest-based advertising to users, DoubleClick must recognize the respective DoubleClick must be able to recognize the respective viewer and associate the web pages visited, clicks and other information on user behavior with him. For this purpose, DoubleClick uses cookies or comparable recognition technologies (e.g. device fingerprinting). The information collected is combined into a pseudonymous user profile in order to display interest-based advertising to the relevant user.

The use of this service is based on your consent in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR and 25 Para. 1 TTDSG. The consent can be revoked at any time.

For more information on how to object to the advertisements displayed by Google, see the following links advertisements displayed by Google can be found in the following links: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/](https://policies.google.com/technologies/)ads and [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).

Zendesk
-------

We use the CRM system Zendesk to process user inquiries. The provider is Zendesk, Inc, 1019 Market Street in San Francisco, CA 94103 USA.

We use Zendesk to process your inquiries quickly and efficiently. This constitutes a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. You can only send inquiries by entering your email address and without providing your name. The messages sent to us will remain with us until you ask us to delete them or the purpose for data storage no longer applies (e.g. after your request has been processed). Mandatory legal provisions – in particular retention periods – remain unaffected.

Zendesk has Binding Corporate Rules (BCR) that have been approved by the Irish Data Protection Authority. These are binding corporate rules that legitimize the internal transfer of data to third countries outside the EU and the EEA. Details can be found here: [https://www.zendesk.de/blog/update-privacy-shield-invalidation-european-court-justice/](https://www.zendesk.de/blog/update-privacy-shield-invalidation-european-court-justice/).

If you do not agree to your request being processed by us via Zendesk, you can alternatively communicate with us by email, telephone or fax.

Further information can be found in Zendesk’s privacy policy: [https://www.zendesk.de/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/](https://www.zendesk.de/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/).

Our website offers you the option of sending us messages via a chat window. The chat functions are provided by Zendesk. If you use this chat window, we store your IP address in addition to your chat messages. It is not necessary to provide your name for the chat.

We have concluded a data processing agreement (DPA) with the above-mentioned provider. This is a contract required by data protection law, which ensures that the provider only processes the personal data of our website visitors in accordance with our instructions and in compliance with the GDPR.

SOCIAL PLUGINS VON FACEBOOK, TWITTER, INSTAGRAM, PINTEREST, XING, ADDTHIS, WHATSAPP ETC.
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Social buttons from social networks are used on our website. These are only integrated into the page as HTML links, so that when you call up our website, no connection is yet established with the servers of the respective provider. If you click on one of the buttons, the website of the respective social network opens in a new window of your browser There you can, for example, press the Like or Share button.

USE OF PERSONAL DATA IN THE APPLICATION PROCESS
-----------------------------------------------

**Purpose of data collection**

We generally use your personal data to respond to your inquiry, process your order, or provide you with access to specific information or offers. Further information on data protection can also be found on this website. However, we would also like to facilitate your job search. You can therefore apply for jobs with us directly online or by e-mail. We assure you that your data will be treated confidentially. The data you provide will be processed and used exclusively for the purpose of selecting applicants.

**What data is collected?**

We only collect the information required for an application process with us.  
When you apply for a position with us, you will be asked for certain personal data (name, address, e-mail). In addition, position-related questions may be asked. For an application at our company, it is also mandatory to include your professional background.  
Please note that your data will not be stored anonymously, but will be accessible to the HR department and to the departments at our company that are relevant to the position.

**Application information**

By submitting your application, you represent that the information you have provided is true and accurate. Please note that any false statement or omission may be grounds for rejection or subsequent dismissal.  
We seek applicants regardless of race, ethnicity, gender, religion, belief, disability, age or sexual identity. We do not require any information from you that is not usable under the General Equal Treatment Act. Please also do not forward to us any confidential internal information or even trade secrets of your former or current employer. In addition, please do not provide any unnecessary information regarding: Illnesses, pregnancy, ethnic origin, political views, philosophical or religious beliefs, trade union membership, physical or mental health, sex life, defamatory or honorable information, as well as information that has nothing to do with the job profile.

**Who processes the data?**

The data we collect is processed exclusively internally or by contractually affiliated service providers. Personal data is only passed on for specific purposes within the framework of order processing in accordance with data protection regulations to bodies that, for example, operate our servers or provide certain services. These bodies are located in Germany and in the countries of the EU and are bound by contractual obligations and data protection instructions to handle personal data in accordance with data protection law.  
The data and files you provide will be processed and used exclusively for the purpose of processing your application. The data and files you provide may, if your application is successful, be further processed and used by us in an employment relationship for employment purposes. If the application for a job offer is unsuccessful, we will store the submitted data and files in an applicant database for six months in order to be able to answer subsequent questions about the application. After six months, the data and files are deleted. It is possible to withdraw the application at any time. If you withdraw your application, your data and files will be deleted from the applicant database immediately, subject to the restrictions listed below. Furthermore, as part of the application process, you can request at any time that individual data or files you have submitted to us be deleted. However, we reserve the right to store a limited amount of your data for a limited period of three months in order to comply with legal requirements, in particular obligations to provide evidence under the General Equal Treatment Act (AGG).

**With whom do we share your personal data?**

The information you provide to us will be treated confidentially and will only be passed on to those persons who are involved in a specific application process. Your personal data will only be passed on to other Group companies with your separate, explicit consent.  
Please refer to the relevant notice on this website.

**Right of access, editing and deletion of your resume**

You can access, edit or delete your resume at any time. You may also ask us to assist you in doing so.  
Please understand that, for legal reasons, it is not possible to change or delete data during an ongoing application process or for a period of approximately three months after the end of an ongoing application process.

Security
--------

We have implemented technical and administrative security measures to protect your personal data against loss, destruction, manipulation and unauthorized access. All our employees and service providers working for us are bound by the applicable data protection laws.

Whenever we collect and process personal data, it is encrypted before it is transmitted. This means that your data cannot be misused by third parties. Our security measures are subject to a continuous improvement process and our data protection statements are constantly being revised. Please make sure that you have the latest version.

Rights of the data subject
--------------------------

You have a right to information, correction, deletion or restriction of the processing of your stored data at any time, a right to object to the processing as well as a right to data portability and to lodge a complaint in accordance with the requirements of data protection law.

### Right of access by the data subjec:

You can request information from us as to whether and to what extent we process your data.

### Right to rectification:

If we process your data that is incomplete or incorrect, you can request that we correct or complete it at any time.

### Right to erasure (right to be forgotten):

You can demand that we delete your data if we process it unlawfully or if the processing disproportionately interferes with your legitimate interests in protection. Please note that there may be reasons that prevent immediate deletion, e.g. in the case of legally regulated retention obligations.

Irrespective of the exercise of your right to deletion, we will delete your data immediately and completely, provided that there is no legal or statutory obligation to retain data in this respect.

### Right to restriction of the processing:

You may request us to restrict the processing of your data if.

* you dispute the accuracy of the data, for a period of time that allows us to verify the accuracy of the data.
* the processing of the data is unlawful, but you refuse erasure and request restriction of data use instead,
* we no longer need the data for the intended purpose, but you still need this data to assert or defend legal claims, or
* you have objected to the processing of the data.

### Right to data portability:

You may request that we provide you with your data that you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and that you may transfer this data to another controller without hindrance from us, provided that

* we process this data on the basis of a revocable consent given by you or for the performance of a contract between us, and
* this processing is carried out with the aid of automated procedures.

If technically feasible, you may request us to transfer your data directly to another controller.

### Right to object:

If we process your data for legitimate interest, you may object to this data processing at any time; this would also apply to profiling based on these provisions. We will then no longer process your data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing that override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the assertion, exercise or defense of legal claims. You may object to the processing of your data for the purpose of direct marketing at any time without giving reasons.

### Right of complaint:

If you are of the opinion that we violate German or European data protection law when processing your data, please contact us to clarify any questions. Of course, you also have the right to contact the supervisory authority responsible for you, the respective state office for data protection supervision.  
If you wish to assert any of the aforementioned rights against us, please contact our data protection officer. In case of doubt, we may request additional information to confirm your identity.

Duty to inform according to Art. 13 DS-GVO
------------------------------------------

Changes to this privacy policy
------------------------------

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy if necessary due to new technologies. Please make sure that you have the most current version. If fundamental changes are made to this privacy statement, we will announce them on our website.

All interested parties and visitors to our website can contact us regarding data protection issues at:

Mr Matthias Haßler LL.M.  
Project 29 GmbH & Co. KG  
Ostengasse 14  
93047 Regensburg, Germany

Tel.: +49 941 2986930  
Fax: +49 941 29869316  
Email: anfragen@projekt29.de  
Internet: www.projekt29.de

Change your privacy settings
----------------------------

If required you can or .

Your user ID for data protection issues:

This might be interesting
-------------------------

### Professional support

Get the expertise of our MediaWiki experts and BlueSpice developers.

### Migration

Our experts will support you in moving your data.

### Templates

The user-friendly introduction to BlueSpice.

### FAQ

Find the right answer to your question here.

### Data protection & security

BlueSpice protects you from external attacks and takes into account the requirements of the GDPR.

### Edition comparison

BlueSpice free, pro and farm.

### Authentication server connection

Log in automatically and get started right away.

### Trust & Safety

For satisfied users and secure software.

BlueSpice News & Know How

### Product info, webinars, events and more.

Ms./Mr. \*

\-Ms.Mr.

Title

\-Dr.Prof.Prof. Dr.

First name \*

Last name \*

E-mail adresse \*

Privacy \*

I accept the privacy policy

Thank you for your message.

×

There was an error trying to send your message. Please try again later.

×

Subscribe now

0

years of experience

0

countries worldwide

0

enterprise extensions

0

employees

0

downloads

#### [Get started](#d8a784889409dd227)

#### [Ressourcen](#3571772bc3740d875)

#### [Community](#bf0f4273cb2e6819d)

#### [BlueSpice](#ee24cd3942fa6bfbb)

#### [Company](#ece5b53ad499484cd)

* **Get started**

* **Ressources**

* **Community**

* **BlueSpice**

* **Company**

BlueSpice is a brand of Hallo Welt! GmbH, a worldwide leading provider and consultant for MediaWiki solutions

Test Block PopUp
